This is a single call to ID3DXFont::DrawText() with a large text buffer.  It shows that ID3DXFont supports word wrapping.  If you resize the window, the words will automatically wrap to the next line.  It also supports 
hard line breaks.  It also shows that ID3DXFont supports Unicode text with correct word wraping for right-to-left languages.  For example, if you install files for East Asian languages will see Japanese text below:
このサンプルは、テキストの書き方を示しています。

